# **Christian Kouris**

804 Carnaros • San Clemente, CA • 92672 • 949-444-9796 • christiankouris13@gmail.com

## **Summary**

A hardworking and motivated student who strives for excellence. Currently a student at UC San Diego pursuing a degree in computer engineering, whose goal is to work with experienced engineers that will utilize my background and skills.

## **Skills and Qualifications**

- Proficiency in the C family of programming languages including C, C++, and Java.
- Experience in Python, Node.js, and React.js
- Worked with the low level languages SystemVerilog and ARM architecture assembly
- Knowledge of Electrostatics and Magnetism
- Seal of Biliteracy; Spanish

# **Projects**

- Worked with a team of 10 to create a full stack web application using Node/React/Express hosted on a Firebase database. The team used agile development to make the application and an MVC model for better security.
- Created an AI that can play Gomoku using Monte Carlo Tree Search
- Used System verilog to create a sha256 encrypter and a 6-tap linear feedback shift register encrypter and decrypter
- Created a C++ program that uses UCS in a graph to connect actors through the movies they acted in

## **Education**

## University of California, San Diego

9/2017 - 3/2021

Bachelor of Science, Computer Engineering

#### Awards

• Provost Honors

# **Experience**

GoVyrl 6/2019 - 8/2019

#### Intern

- Assisted a team of around 30 developers in creating optimizations to a database of over 1 million customers
- Created multiple development environments using AWS and Buddy-Works
- Created Python scripts to interact with the AWS Parameter Store in order to increase parameter readability

## **National Honors Society**

1/2016 - 6/2017

- Organized fundraisers
- Volunteered at holiday toy drives
- Coordinated horticulture renovation on campus

Chamber Orchestra 2006-Present

Performed in professional level concerts; Volunteered for funeral services and charity events; Cellist